[
  {
    "id": "naruto-001",
    "question": "When did Obito first awaken his mangekyou sharingan",
    "options": ["when he killed his best friend", "when he saw rin get killed", "when rin was captured", "when kakashi´s eye was slashed"],
    "answer": "when he saw rin get killed",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-002",
    "question": "Which of the following is not a ninja from the hidden stone village",
    "options": ["Akatsuchi", "Kurotsuchi", "Deidara", "Matsuchi"],
    "answer": "Matsuchi",
    "difficulty": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-003",
    "question": "Who is the wielder of fang, the boltsword",
    "options": ["ameyuri ringo", "jinin akebino", "jinpachi", "hozuki"],
    "answer": "ameyuri ringo",
    "difficulty": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-004",
    "question": "Which of the following isn’t part of Kakashi's ninja dogs",
    "options": ["pakkun", "akino", "guruko", "Jinuki"],
    "answer": "Jinuki",
    "difficulty": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-005",
    "question": "Pakkun refers to his paws as",
    "options": ["soft", "pura pura", "puri puri", "puro puro"],
    "answer": "puri puri",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-006",
    "question": "What is the name of Pakkun's shampoo",
    "options": ["floral green", "floral blue", "floral red", "floral pink"],
    "answer": "floral green",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-007",
    "question": "With whom does Pakkun share the same shampoo?",
    "options": ["Ino", "Sakura", "kakashi's other dogs", "kakashi"],
    "answer": "Sakura",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-008",
    "question": "What is the ability of Pain's Animal Path?",
    "options": ["absorbing ones jutsus", "shinra tensei", "summonings", "missiles"],
    "answer": "summonings",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-009",
    "question": "What is Anko's last name?",
    "options": ["Masashi", "Misashi", "Matarashi", "Mitarashi"],
    "answer": "Mitarashi",
    "difficulty": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-010",
    "question": "At what age did Anko become a genin",
    "options": ["9", "10", "11", "12"],
    "answer": "10",
    "difficulty": "expert"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-011",
    "question": "Who discovered that Danzou was cheating at the HOKAGE summit?",
    "options": ["Chojuro", "Mifune", "Ao", "Raikage"],
    "answer": "Ao",
    "difficulty": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-012",
    "question": "What is the name of Ao's partner at the summit",
    "options": ["Chojuro", "Akatsuchi", "MIzukage", "Kankurou"],
    "answer": "Chojuro",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-013",
    "question": "What is Asuma´s relationship to Konohamaru",
    "options": ["His godfather", "his uncle", "his cousin", "His nephew"],
    "answer": "his uncle",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-014",
    "question": "Who was Asuma's closest friend in the twelve guardian ninjas",
    "options": ["Kazuma", "Chiriku", "Kitane", "Korune"],
    "answer": "Chiriku",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-015",
    "question": "Why did Asuma leave Konoha to join the twelve guardian ninjas",
    "options": ["he was tired of Konoha", "his father wanted him to join", "he wanted to protect the king", "he had an argument with his father"],
    "answer": "he had an argument with his father",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-016",
    "question": "How much is the bounty on Asuma's head",
    "options": ["25 million ryou", "35 million ryou", "45 million ryou", "55million ryou"],
    "answer": "35 million ryou",
    "difficulty": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-017",
    "question": "Who did Shikamaru fight in the second round of the chuunin exams",
    "options": ["Dosu", "Temari", "Yorui", "kin"],
    "answer": "kin",
    "difficulty": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-018",
    "question": "Who was the only member of Team 10 to win in the third round of the chuunin exams",
    "options": ["Shikamaru", "Ino", "Chouji", "Shino"],
    "answer": "Shikamaru",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-019",
    "question": "What is the name of Gaara's tailed beast",
    "options": ["Shukaku", "Shikaku", "Shakaku", "Shukaki"],
    "answer": "Shukaku",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-020",
    "question": "Which of Kisame's moves did Kakashi first use against him when they invaded Konoha during the chuunin exams",
    "options": ["Water Dragon", "Suiton Suishoha", "Suiton Hahonryou", "Water Shark Missile"],
    "answer": "Water Shark Missile",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-021",
    "question": "Which of the sound four did Chouji face on Sasuke's rescue mission",
    "options": ["Dosu", "Jiroubou", "Tayuya", "Sakon"],
    "answer": "Jiroubou",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-022",
    "question": "Which village is Kin from",
    "options": ["Sound", "Leaf", "Sand", "Rain"],
    "answer": "Sound",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-023",
    "question": "Sora is the son of which twelve guardian ninja",
    "options": ["Kazuma", "Chiruku", "Kitane", "Korune"],
    "answer": "Kazuma",
    "difficulty": "expert"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-024",
    "question": "What is the name of the jutsu that the ninja guardians wanted to use to destroy Konoha",
    "options": ["Raiton Judgement", "Shockwave", "Limelight", "Tornado Storm"],
    "answer": "Limelight",
    "difficulty": "expert"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-025",
    "question": "Which of the following is not a member of the twelve ninja guardians",
    "options": ["Chiruku", "Kazuma", "Kitane", "Korune"],
    "answer": "Korune",
    "difficulty": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-026",
    "question": "What is the name of the team the Hokage assembled to track and kill Akatsuki",
    "options": ["Niju Shotai", "Elite Guardians", "Twelve Ninja Guardians", "Shishikubi"],
    "answer": "Niju Shotai",
    "difficulty": "expert"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-027",
    "question": "Which of the following is not one of the paths of Pain",
    "options": ["Animal Path", "Asura Path", "Naraka Path", "Death Path"],
    "answer": "Death Path",
    "difficulty": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-028",
    "question": "Who is the jounin leader of Gaara, Temari and Kankurou",
    "options": ["Baki", "Baku", "Baka", "Bako"],
    "answer": "Baki",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-029",
    "question": "What is the name of Kakashi's largest dog",
    "options": ["Pitbull", "Bulldog", "Bull", "Biscuit"],
    "answer": "Bull",
    "difficulty": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-030",
    "question": "What is Chouji's father's name",
    "options": ["Akimichi", "Chouza", "Chouba", "Chouja"],
    "answer": "Chouza",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-031",
    "question": "What is the name of Hiruzen's wife",
    "options": ["Biwako", "Nara", "Hasane", "Kurana"],
    "answer": "Biwako",
    "difficulty": "expert"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-032",
    "question": "What is the name of Chojuro's sword",
    "options": ["Akebino", "Hiramakarei", "Helmet splitter", "needle"],
    "answer": "Hiramakarei",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-033",
    "question": "Who is the lead monk of the fire temple and one of the twelve guardian ninjas",
    "options": ["Chiriku", "Hidan", "Kagane", "kasami"],
    "answer": "Chiriku",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-034",
    "question": "What is the name of Elder Chiyo of the sand´s brother",
    "options": ["Sanzu", "Ebizo", "Tani", "Chinzu"],
    "answer": "Ebizo",
    "difficulty": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-035",
    "question": "Which of the following is not a citizen of the Land of Water",
    "options": ["Yamabuki", "Inari", "Akane", "Akaboshi"],
    "answer": "Akaboshi",
    "difficulty": "expert"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-036",
    "question": "What is the name of the move Chojuro used at the summit against Sasuke",
    "options": ["Hiramakarei release", "Hiramakarei extend", "Hiramakarei destroy", "Hiramakarei shoha"],
    "answer": "Hiramakarei release",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-037",
    "question": "What is the name of the 7 tails beast",
    "options": ["Fuu", "Chomei", "Son Goku", "Ukitake"],
    "answer": "Chomei",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-038",
    "question": "What is the name of the 7 tails Jinchuuriki",
    "options": ["Fuu", "Chomei", "Son Goku", "Ukitake"],
    "answer": "Fuu",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-039",
    "question": "Who is the real Tobi",
    "options": ["Obito", "Madara", "Sasori", "Deidara"],
    "answer": "Obito",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-040",
    "question": "Who was Orochimaru's partner at Akatsuki",
    "options": ["Itachi", "Sasori", "Hidan", "Kakuzu"],
    "answer": "Sasori",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-041",
    "question": "Which of the following is the name of Tsunade's lover",
    "options": ["Dan", "Jiraiya", "Orochimaru", "San"],
    "answer": "Dan",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-042",
    "question": "Who was the great leader of Amegakure",
    "options": ["Danzou", "Hanzou", "Ohnoki", "Orochimaru"],
    "answer": "Hanzou",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-043",
    "question": "Who defeated the resurrected Hanzou during the ninja war",
    "options": ["Mifune", "Guy", "Kakashi", "Gaara"],
    "answer": "Mifune",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-044",
    "question": "What is Hanzou's summoning",
    "options": ["salamander", "Chameleon", "Elephant", "Tortoise"],
    "answer": "salamander",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-045",
    "question": "Who was the Uchiha clan leader during Hiruzen's time",
    "options": ["Fugaku", "Madara", "Shisui", "Dara"],
    "answer": "Fugaku",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-047",
    "question": "What is the name of the revered frog village",
    "options": ["Myoubuku", "Kotosan", "Amegakure", "Shotan"],
    "answer": "Myoubuku",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-048",
    "question": "Who was first nominated to be the sixth Hokage",
    "options": ["Danzou", "Tsunade", "Shikaku", "Kakashi"],
    "answer": "Kakashi",
    "difficulty": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-049",
    "question": "Which village were the assassins from that attacked Danzou as he prepared to leave for the Hokage summit",
    "options": ["Land of Stone", "Land of Wood", "Land of Rain", "Land of Iron"],
    "answer": "Land of Wood",
    "difficulty": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-050",
    "question": "Who is the leader of the Land of Iron",
    "options": ["Hanzou", "Mifune", "Akaboshi", "Ai"],
    "answer": "Mifune",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-051",
    "question": "What is the name of the mercenary organizations that wanted to capture tailed beasts",
    "options": ["Akatsuki", "Akatsuka", "Niju Shotai", "Shishikubi"],
    "answer": "Akatsuki",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-052",
    "question": "Who was Naruto's first kiss",
    "options": ["Sasuke", "Sakura", "Ino", "Hinata"],
    "answer": "Sasuke",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-053",
    "question": "What is the name of Naruto's father",
    "options": ["Minato", "Jiraiya", "Hiruzen", "Kakashi"],
    "answer": "Minato",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-054",
    "question": "What is Sakura's surname",
    "options": ["Haruno", "Inamaka", "Haruna", "Nara"],
    "answer": "Haruno",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-055",
    "question": "Who was in possession of Shisui's eyesat the beginning.",
    "options": ["Madara", "Sasuke", "Itachi", "Danzou"],
    "answer": "Danzou",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-057",
    "question": "What is the name of Danzou's summoning",
    "options": ["Baki", "Baku", "Hagi", "Hisagi"],
    "answer": "Baku",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-058",
    "question": "What is the name of the seal Danzou used in a last ditch effort to kill both Sasuke and Madara",
    "options": ["Reverse one point symbol", "Reverse two point seal", "Reverse three symbols seal", "Reverse four symbols seal"],
    "answer": "Reverse four symbols seal",
    "difficulty": "expert"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-059",
    "question": "Which of the following isn’t a user of Sanjou Rashomon",
    "options": ["Orochimaru", "Hashirama", "Sound 4", "Kabuto"],
    "answer": "Kabuto",
    "difficulty": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-060",
    "question": "Who is the commander of the First Division during the shinobi world war",
    "options": ["Kakashi", "Darui", "Gaara", "Raikage"],
    "answer": "Darui",
    "difficulty": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-061",
    "question": "What is the name of Naruto's special jounin instructor",
    "options": ["Iruka", "Mizuki", "Ebisu", "Kakashi"],
    "answer": "Ebisu",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-062",
    "question": "Who killed Deidara",
    "options": ["Sasuke", "Madara", "Kakashi", "Gai"],
    "answer": "Sasuke",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-063",
    "question": "Which Jinchuuriki did Deidara capture",
    "options": ["Naruto", "Killerbee", "Fuu", "Gaara"],
    "answer": "Gaara",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-064",
    "question": "Who did Deidara lose his second arm to",
    "options": ["Kakashi", "Gai", "Gaara", "Sasuke"],
    "answer": "Kakashi",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-065",
    "question": "Which tailed beast were Tobi and Deidara sent to capture",
    "options": ["Two tails", "Three tails", "Four tails", "Five tails"],
    "answer": "Three tails",
    "difficulty": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-066",
    "question": "Where did Sasuke learn the move that saved him from Itachi's Amaterasu",
    "options": ["Kakashi", "Orochimaru", "Itachi", "Suigetsu"],
    "answer": "Orochimaru",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-067",
    "question": "Which of the following is not a member of Sasuke's group",
    "options": ["Juugo", "Kirin", "Suigetsu", "Karin"],
    "answer": "Kirin",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-068",
    "question": "What is the name of Sasuke's ultimate destructive lightning move",
    "options": ["Kirin", "Chidori", "Chidori senbon", "Chidori nagashi"],
    "answer": "Kirin",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-069",
    "question": "Juugo joined Sasuke's group because",
    "options": ["he believed in him", "he had nowhere else to go", "he reminded him of kimimaro", "he could stop his rage"],
    "answer": "he reminded him of kimimaro",
    "difficulty": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-070",
    "question": "What is the name of the ninja cat that lives at Uchiha supply base",
    "options": ["Senka", "Henka", "Enka", "Denka"],
    "answer": "Denka",
    "difficulty": "expert"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-071",
    "question": "Who did Orochimaru order to kill Sasuke during the chuunin exams",
    "options": ["Kabuto", "Kin", "Dosu", "Yorui"],
    "answer": "Dosu",
    "difficulty": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-072",
    "question": "Which of the following isn’t a student of Killer Bee",
    "options": ["Samui", "Omoi", "Karui", "Darui"],
    "answer": "Darui",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-073",
    "question": "Who killed the Fourth Kazekage",
    "options": ["Pein", "Orochimaru", "Sasori", "Madara"],
    "answer": "Orochimaru",
    "difficulty": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-074",
    "question": "Fuu(Danzou´s guard) is a member of which clan",
    "options": ["Yamanaka", "Nara", "Hyuuga", "Aburame"],
    "answer": "Yamanaka",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-075",
    "question": "Ensui(who fought Zabuza with Kakashi during the war) was a member of which clan",
    "options": ["Yamanaka", "Nara", "Hyuuga", "Aburame"],
    "answer": "Nara",
    "difficulty": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-076",
    "question": "Who is the original wielder of Samehada",
    "options": ["Kisame", "Zabuza", "Akebino", "Fuguki"],
    "answer": "Fuguki",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-077",
    "question": "Who tried to teach Naruto how to use sage mode",
    "options": ["Fukasaku", "Jiraiya", "Gamabunta", "Shima"],
    "answer": "Fukasaku",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-078",
    "question": "Which one of the following isn’t one of Jiraiya's toads",
    "options": ["Gamabunta", "Gamaken", "Gamakun", "Gamakichi"],
    "answer": "Gamakun",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-079",
    "question": "What is the name of Fukasaku's(elder sage toad) wife",
    "options": ["Shima", "Shimura", "Shi", "Shimu"],
    "answer": "Shima",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-080",
    "question": "Which of the six paths of Pain was sent by Jiraiya to Konoha for study",
    "options": ["Animal path", "Asura Path", "Naraka Path", "Deva path"],
    "answer": "Animal path",
    "difficulty": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-081",
    "question": "Where was Naruto when Fukasaku summoned him on the orders of the great toad sage",
    "options": ["Hokage's office", "training with Kakashi", "with Sakura", "Ichiraku Ramen"],
    "answer": "Ichiraku Ramen",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-082",
    "question": "The seven-tailed beast is a",
    "options": ["monkey", "an ox", "beetle", "cat"],
    "answer": "beetle",
    "difficulty": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-083",
    "question": "What is the name of Gaara's uncle",
    "options": ["Baki", "Yashamaru", "Yoshimaru", "Kankurou"],
    "answer": "Yashamaru",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-084",
    "question": "Who tried to kill Gaara when he was young",
    "options": ["Yashamaru", "Yoshamaru", "his father", "Baki"],
    "answer": "Yashamaru",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-085",
    "question": "Which of the following is Gamabunta's kid",
    "options": ["Gamakichi and Gamaken", "Gamatatsu and Gamaken", "Gamakichi and Gamatatsu", "Gamatatsu and Gamabun"],
    "answer": "Gamakichi and Gamatatsu",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-086",
    "question": "What is the name of Tsunade's summon",
    "options": ["Kaguya", "Kaguyu", "Katsuya", "Katsuyu"],
    "answer": "Katsuyu",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-087",
    "question": "What is Gamabunta's weapon of choice",
    "options": ["a scythe", "a dagger", "a spear", "a shuriken"],
    "answer": "a dagger",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-088",
    "question": "Who did Naruto first summon when facing Gaara after the chuunin exams",
    "options": ["Gamabunta", "Gamakichi", "Gamaken", "Gamatatsu"],
    "answer": "Gamakichi",
    "difficulty": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-089",
    "question": "What is the name of Orochimaru's great snake",
    "options": ["Manda", "Sanbi", "Habi", "Chimaru"],
    "answer": "Manda",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-090",
    "question": "Who summoned Manda for the last time before his death",
    "options": ["Sasuke", "Kabuto", "Orochimaru", "Itachi"],
    "answer": "Sasuke",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-091",
    "question": "Which of the following is the clumsy frog/toad",
    "options": ["Gamabunta", "Gamatatsu", "Gamakichi", "Gamaken"],
    "answer": "Gamaken",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-092",
    "question": "What is the name of Gamabunta's second son",
    "options": ["Gamaken", "Gamakichi", "Gamatatsu", "Gamabun"],
    "answer": "Gamatatsu",
    "difficulty": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-093",
    "question": "Who was the criminal that ultimately had Zabuza killed on the bridge",
    "options": ["Hanori", "Yushimaru", "Gato", "Basu"],
    "answer": "Gato",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-094",
    "question": "What is the name of the bridge builder and Inari's grandfather",
    "options": ["Hazuna", "Gato", "Tazuna", "Biku"],
    "answer": "Tazuna",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-095",
    "question": "What is the name of Zabuza's companion",
    "options": ["Haku", "Haki", "Baku", "Baki"],
    "answer": "Haku",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-096",
    "question": "What is Haku's kekkei genkai",
    "options": ["a tailed beast", "sharingan", "ice", "bones"],
    "answer": "ice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-097",
    "question": "What is Kimimaro's kekkei genkai",
    "options": ["a tailed beast", "sharingan", "ice", "bones"],
    "answer": "bones",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-098",
    "question": "Who is the examiner that took over for Hayate at the chuunin exams after he was killed",
    "options": ["Genma", "Iruka", "Ebisu", "Gekko"],
    "answer": "Genma",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-099",
    "question": "Who killed the examiner Hayate at the chuunin exams",
    "options": ["Garui", "Gaara", "Kabuto", "Baki"],
    "answer": "Baki",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-100",
    "question": "What is the name of the toad that holds the key to Naruto's 8 trigam seal",
    "options": ["Fukasaku", "Tora", "Asake", "Geratora"],
    "answer": "Geratora",
    "difficulty": "expert"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-101",
    "question": "Who is the person that Orochimaru had to use as a vessel prior to Sasuke's arrival",
    "options": ["Guren", "Genyumaru", "Guki", "Kinaki"],
    "answer": "Genyumaru",
    "difficulty": "expert"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-102",
    "question": "Kinkaku and Ginkaku are from which village",
    "options": ["Hidden leaf", "Hidden Rain", "Hidden stone", "Hidden cloud"],
    "answer": "Hidden cloud",
    "difficulty": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-103",
    "question": "Kinkaku and Ginkaku are known as the",
    "options": ["Gold and Bronze brothers", "Silver and Gold brothers", "the deadly duo", "Gold brothers"],
    "answer": "Silver and Gold brothers",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-104",
    "question": "What is Guren's kekkei genkai",
    "options": ["mirrors", "ice", "crystals", "diamonds"],
    "answer": "crystals",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-105",
    "question": "Who did Orochimaru task with capturing the three tails",
    "options": ["Kabuto", "Guren", "the sound four", "Kimimaro"],
    "answer": "Guren",
    "difficulty": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-106",
    "question": "After Kimimaro's illness was discovered who was chosen to be Orochimaru's next vessel",
    "options": ["Guren", "Kabuto", "Sasuke", "Juugo"],
    "answer": "Guren",
    "difficulty": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-107",
    "question": "What is the 8-tails ox's name",
    "options": ["Killerbee", "Gyuki", "Ibuki", "Byuki"],
    "answer": "Gyuki",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-108",
    "question": "Who is the Jinchuuriki of the five tails",
    "options": ["Ukitaka", "Yugito", "Han", "Yagura"],
    "answer": "Han",
    "difficulty": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-109",
    "question": "What is the name of Kiba's elder sister",
    "options": ["Hana", "Kin", "Yasha", "Maru"],
    "answer": "Hana",
    "difficulty": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-110",
    "question": "The Jinchuuriki of the five tails is from which village",
    "options": ["Hidden leaf", "Hidden stone", "Hidden mist", "Hidden rain"],
    "answer": "Hidden stone",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-111",
    "question": "Where is Haku from",
    "options": ["Land of stone", "Land of sound", "Land of rain", "Land of mist"],
    "answer": "Land of mist",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-112",
    "question": "What is Zabuza's surname",
    "options": ["Demon", "Hochi", "Hozuki", "Momochi"],
    "answer": "Momochi",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-113",
    "question": "Who is Neji's uncle as well as the leader of the Hyuga clan",
    "options": ["Hiashi", "Hayashi", "Hyuga", "Hyoshi"],
    "answer": "Hiashi",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-114",
    "question": "What is the name of Hashirama's Deep Forest Emergence technique",
    "options": ["Mokuton no jutsu", "Hiraishin no jutsu", "Jukai Koutan", "Rashoumon"],
    "answer": "Jukai Koutan",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-115",
    "question": "Which of the following Akatsuki members fought Hashirama",
    "options": ["Hidan", "Kakuzu", "Pein", "Kisame"],
    "answer": "Kakuzu",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-116",
    "question": "What is the name of the great monkey summoning of Hiruzen",
    "options": ["Son Goku", "Enma", "Gamabunta", "Baku"],
    "answer": "Enma",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-117",
    "question": "What is the name of Hinata's younger sister",
    "options": ["Kanabi", "Jinora", "Hayate", "Hanabi"],
    "answer": "Hanabi",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-118",
    "question": "Who is Hinata's group leader",
    "options": ["Asuma", "Ebisu", "Kurenai", "Gai"],
    "answer": "Kurenai",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-119",
    "question": "Which of the following is not a member of Hinata's team",
    "options": ["Akamaru", "Shino", "Tenten", "Kiba"],
    "answer": "Tenten",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-120",
    "question": "Which of the following cannot use the First's jutsu",
    "options": ["Madara", "Danzou", "Yamato", "Tobirama"],
    "answer": "Tobirama",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-121",
    "question": "Who tricked Naruto into stealing the forbidden scroll",
    "options": ["Mizuki", "Kurama", "Tengumaru", "Iruka"],
    "answer": "Mizuki",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-122",
    "question": "Who created the Hidden Sound Village",
    "options": ["Pein", "Orochimaru", "Hayate", "Karate"],
    "answer": "Orochimaru",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-123",
    "question": "What is the first jutsu Hiruzen used in the fight against Orochimaru",
    "options": ["Shuriken no jutsu", "Roof Tile Shuriken", "Doton Doryun Heki", "Earth Swamp"],
    "answer": "Roof Tile Shuriken",
    "difficulty": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-124",
    "question": "Hidan is Kakuzu’s partner because....",
    "options": ["he loves killing as much as Kakuzu does", "they are compatible", "Hidan can't be killed", "they both loved money"],
    "answer": "Hidan can't be killed",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-125",
    "question": "Which god does Hidan serve",
    "options": ["Akatsuki", "Jashin", "Huushi", "Bushido"],
    "answer": "Jashin",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-126",
    "question": "What is Hidan's weapon of choice",
    "options": ["a scythe", "a sword", "a spear", "a kunai"],
    "answer": "a scythe",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-127",
    "question": "Hidan and Kakuzu were tasked with capturing",
    "options": ["two tails", "three tails", "four tails", "five tails"],
    "answer": "two tails",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-128",
    "question": "What was the first move Chouji used against Kakuzu",
    "options": ["Baika no jutsu", "Nikudan Harisensha", "Rolling thunder", "Cannon Bolt"],
    "answer": "Nikudan Harisensha",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-129",
    "question": "What is the name of the two tails Jinchuuriki",
    "options": ["Roshi", "Yagura", "Utakata", "Yugito"],
    "answer": "Yugito",
    "difficulty": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-130",
    "question": "How many hearts does Kakuzu have in total",
    "options": ["4", "5", "6", "3"],
    "answer": "5",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-131",
    "question": "Who killed Kakuzu",
    "options": ["Naruto", "Kakashi", "Shikamaru", "Asuma"],
    "answer": "Naruto",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-132",
    "question": "What does Hidan call his immortality technique",
    "options": ["Reaper seal", "Jashin's revenge", "Jashin's curse", "Jashin's wrath"],
    "answer": "Jashin's curse",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-133",
    "question": "Who is Neji's father",
    "options": ["Hyuga", "Hiashi", "Hizashi", "Hashi"],
    "answer": "Hizashi",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-134",
    "question": "What is Ibiki's surname",
    "options": ["Moreno", "Morino", "Yashamaru", "Yushimaru"],
    "answer": "Morino",
    "difficulty": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-135",
    "question": "Who is the head of Konoha´s Torture and Interrogation Unit",
    "options": ["Ibiki", "Hayate", "Inoichi", "Pein"],
    "answer": "Ibiki",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-136",
    "question": "What is the name of Hanzou's salamander",
    "options": ["Ibuse", "Kin", "Sanzou", "Tengu"],
    "answer": "Ibuse",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-137",
    "question": "What is Ino's father's name",
    "options": ["Ibiki", "Shikaku", "Inoichi", "Inozuki"],
    "answer": "Inoichi",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-138",
    "question": "What is Ino's surname",
    "options": ["Inoichi", "Yamanaka", "Nara", "Akimichi"],
    "answer": "Yamanaka",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-139",
    "question": "What is Chouji's surname",
    "options": ["Nara", "Akimichi", "Akamachi", "Yamanaka"],
    "answer": "Akimichi",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-140",
    "question": "What is the name of the three-tailed turtle bijuu",
    "options": ["Gyuki", "Son Goku", "Chomei", "Isobu"],
    "answer": "Isobu",
    "difficulty": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-141",
    "question": "What is the name of the three tails Jinchuuriki",
    "options": ["Yugito", "Yagura", "Utakata", "Roshi"],
    "answer": "Yagura",
    "difficulty": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-142",
    "question": "Who captured Son Goku's Jinchuuriki",
    "options": ["Itachi", "Kisame", "Deidara", "Sasori"],
    "answer": "Kisame",
    "difficulty": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-143",
    "question": "Who is Son Goku's Jinchuuriki",
    "options": ["Roshi", "Yugito", "Yagura", "Utakata"],
    "answer": "Roshi",
    "difficulty": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-144",
    "question": "Who willingly gave Madara his eyes when he started to go blind",
    "options": ["Shisui", "Fugaku", "Izuna", "Kin"],
    "answer": "Izuna",
    "difficulty": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-145",
    "question": "Which village is the shinobi Jei (who was captured by Sasuke and Jugo) from",
    "options": ["Hidden leaf", "Hidden cloud", "Hidden rain", "Hidden stone"],
    "answer": "Hidden cloud",
    "difficulty": "expert"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-146",
    "question": "Who is the wielder of Helmsplitter, the Bluntsword",
    "options": ["Akebino", "Zabuza", "Kushimaru", "Jinpachi"],
    "answer": "Akebino",
    "difficulty": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-147",
    "question": "What is Kabuto's surname",
    "options": ["Yakushi", "Morino", "Yashi", "Tusharu"],
    "answer": "Yakushi",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-148",
    "question": "What is the name of Tsunade's little brother who died in the war",
    "options": ["Dan", "Nawaki", "Hisake", "Torune"],
    "answer": "Nawaki",
    "difficulty": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-149",
    "question": "What is Minato's nickname",
    "options": ["The Flash", "Yellow Flash", "Green Flash", "Red Flash"],
    "answer": "Yellow Flash",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-150",
    "question": "What is Minato's surname",
    "options": ["Uzumaki", "Sarutobi", "Namikaze", "Yellow Flash"],
    "answer": "Namikaze",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-151",
    "question": "Who is Naruto's mother",
    "options": ["Kushina", "Mito", "Saru", "Tosan"],
    "answer": "Kushina",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-152",
    "question": "Who is Naruto's godfather",
    "options": ["Minato", "Jiraiya", "Kakashi", "Sarutobi"],
    "answer": "Jiraiya",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-153",
    "question": "Who is the spider-like user of the Sound Four",
    "options": ["Sakon", "Tayuya", "Jirobou", "Kidoumaru"],
    "answer": "Kidoumaru",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-154",
    "question": "Who is the leader of the Second Division in the Great Ninja War",
    "options": ["Kakashi", "Gaara", "Kitsuchi", "Gai"],
    "answer": "Kitsuchi",
    "difficulty": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-155",
    "question": "What is the name of Sakura's father",
    "options": ["Kizashi", "Haruno", "Hizashi", "Torun"],
    "answer": "Kizashi",
    "difficulty": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-156",
    "question": "Who was the person who ate the forbidden fruit from the Divine Tree and the first person to have chakra in Naruto",
    "options": ["Sage of the Six Paths", "Pein", "Madara", "Kaguya"],
    "answer": "Kaguya",
    "difficulty": "expert"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-157",
    "question": "What is Kakashi's nickname",
    "options": ["Copy Cat", "Copy Ninja", "The flash", "Sharingan"],
    "answer": "Copy Ninja",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-158",
    "question": "What is Kakashi's father's name",
    "options": ["Sakumo", "Hatake", "Hizashi", "Namikaze"],
    "answer": "Sakumo",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-159",
    "question": "What is Kakashi's father known as",
    "options": ["Copy Ninja", "Konoha's White Fang", "Sannin", "Konoha´s Sage"],
    "answer": "Konoha's White Fang",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-160",
    "question": "At what age did Kakashi graduate from the academy",
    "options": ["5", "6", "7", "9"],
    "answer": "5",
    "difficulty": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-161",
    "question": "At what age did Kakashi become a Chunin",
    "options": ["5", "6", "7", "8"],
    "answer": "6",
    "difficulty": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-162",
    "question": "What is the name of the ninja that slashed Kakashi’s eye when he wanted to rescue Rin",
    "options": ["Kakko", "Kakku", "Yashamaru", "Taiseke"],
    "answer": "Taiseke",
    "difficulty": "expert"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-163",
    "question": "What is Kurenai's surname",
    "options": ["Yuuho", "Yuuhi", "Rinaru", "Rinari"],
    "answer": "Yuuhi",
    "difficulty": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-164",
    "question": "What is the name of Kakashi's Mangekyou Sharingan move",
    "options": ["Tsukiyomi", "Eternal Darkness", "Kamui", "Sharingan"],
    "answer": "Kamui",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-165",
    "question": "What was Yamato's Anbu name",
    "options": ["Ao", "Henzou", "Tenzou", "Gyate"],
    "answer": "Tenzou",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-166",
    "question": "What is the name of the young boy Guren fought hard to protect",
    "options": ["Yashamaru", "Yushimaru", "Yukimaru", "Tenzen"],
    "answer": "Yukimaru",
    "difficulty": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-167",
    "question": "Who does Naruto first use his finished Rasen Shuriken move on",
    "options": ["Pein", "Hidan", "Kakuzu", "Yamato"],
    "answer": "Kakuzu",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-168",
    "question": "Which Path of Pein did Kakashi first fight",
    "options": ["Naraka path", "Deva Path", "God path", "Human Path"],
    "answer": "Deva Path",
    "difficulty": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-169",
    "question": "Kakashi was appointed as the leader of which division during the shinobi war",
    "options": ["first", "second", "third", "fourth"],
    "answer": "third",
    "difficulty": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-170",
    "question": "How many jutsu has Kakashi supposedly copied",
    "options": ["100", "1000", "10000", "100000"],
    "answer": "1000",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-171",
    "question": "What is the name of Gaara's mom",
    "options": ["Kazuna", "Karura", "Yushimaru", "Tana"],
    "answer": "Karura",
    "difficulty": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-172",
    "question": "What is the name of Kankuro's defense puppet",
    "options": ["Kuroari", "Crow", "Rashoumon", "Sanshuo"],
    "answer": "Sanshuo",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-173",
    "question": "What was the name of Sasuke's group after they joined Akatsuki",
    "options": ["Hebi", "Rogue 4", "Taka", "Sabu"],
    "answer": "Taka",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-174",
    "question": "Which of the Sound 4 did Kiba fight",
    "options": ["Sakon", "Jirobou", "Kidoumaru", "Tayuya"],
    "answer": "Sakon",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-175",
    "question": "What is the name of Sakon's twin",
    "options": ["Jirobou", "Ukon", "Tayuya", "Kidoumaru"],
    "answer": "Ukon",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-176",
    "question": "Who came to Kiba's rescue during his fight against the Sound 4",
    "options": ["Gaara", "Asuma", "Kankurou", "Temari"],
    "answer": "Kankurou",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-177",
    "question": "What’s the name of Killerbee's Enka master's raccoon",
    "options": ["Ponta", "Sabumaru", "Kin", "Kinta"],
    "answer": "Ponta",
    "difficulty": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-178",
    "question": "Killerbee´s Enka master´s pet Ponta is a",
    "options": ["bear", "salamander", "Shinobi of the leaf", "raccoon"],
    "answer": "raccoon",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-179",
    "question": "What is the name of the five-tailed dolphin horse",
    "options": ["Kokuo", "Chomei", "Gyuki", "Shukaku"],
    "answer": "Kokuo",
    "difficulty": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-180",
    "question": "Who, as a child, asked Haku and Zabuza if they were from the Mist Village during their travels",
    "options": ["Gato", "Kakashi", "Suigetsu", "Kimimaro"],
    "answer": "Kimimaro",
    "difficulty": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-181",
    "question": "Who killed Kisame",
    "options": ["Gai", "Killerbee", "he killed himself", "Raikage"],
    "answer": "he killed himself",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-182",
    "question": "What is the name of the ninja dog with an eye patch from the Inuzuka clan",
    "options": ["Bento", "Kushimaru", "Kuromaru", "Tani"],
    "answer": "Kuromaru",
    "difficulty": "expert"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-183",
    "question": "What is the name of Ohnoki's granddaughter",
    "options": ["Kurotsuchi", "Akatsuchi", "Buchi", "Tana"],
    "answer": "Kurotsuchi",
    "difficulty": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-184",
    "question": "Who is the wielder of Threading Needle, the Long Sword",
    "options": ["Akebino", "Zabuza", "Kushimaru", "Pakura"],
    "answer": "Kushimaru",
    "difficulty": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-185",
    "question": "What is the name of the Fourth Raikage's secretary",
    "options": ["Omoi", "Samui", "Mabui", "Darui"],
    "answer": "Mabui",
    "difficulty": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-186",
    "question": "What is Suigetsu's surname",
    "options": ["Mangetsu", "Hozuki", "Hanara", "Suiton"],
    "answer": "Hozuki",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-187",
    "question": "What is Suigetsu's brother's name",
    "options": ["Mangetsu", "Hozuki", "Hanara", "Suiton"],
    "answer": "Mangetsu",
    "difficulty": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-188",
    "question": "What is the name of the swordsman of the mist who is master of all seven blades",
    "options": ["Mangetsu", "Kisame", "Kaguya", "Hotaru"],
    "answer": "Mangetsu",
    "difficulty": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-189",
    "question": "What is the name of the two-tailed Bijuu",
    "options": ["Kokuo", "Chomei", "Matatabi", "Son Goku"],
    "answer": "Matatabi",
    "difficulty": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-190",
    "question": "What is the name of Sakura's mom",
    "options": ["Mebuki", "Inara", "Soru", "Inaru"],
    "answer": "Mebuki",
    "difficulty": "expert"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-191",
    "question": "What is the name of the Kage of the Mist Village at the Kage summit",
    "options": ["Ibuki", "Hotaru", "Somei", "Mei"],
    "answer": "Mei",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-192",
    "question": "What is the name of Itachi's mother",
    "options": ["Mikoto", "Mebuki", "Mei", "Inaru"],
    "answer": "Mikoto",
    "difficulty": "expert"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-193",
    "question": "What is the name of Konohamaru's female ninja teammate",
    "options": ["Udon", "Moegi", "Motoi", "Dono"],
    "answer": "Moegi",
    "difficulty": "expert"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-194",
    "question": "What is the name of Killerbee's childhood friend",
    "options": ["Ei", "Sakari", "Omoi", "Motoi"],
    "answer": "Motoi",
    "difficulty": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-195",
    "question": "What is the name of the Second Tsuchikage and Ohnoki's mentor",
    "options": ["Mu", "Aoba", "Ai", "Roku"],
    "answer": "Mu",
    "difficulty": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-196",
    "question": "Which of the following paths of Pein is responsible for summoning Outer Path for interrogation and restoration",
    "options": ["Animal Path", "Deva Path", "Human Path", "Naraka Path"],
    "answer": "Naraka Path",
    "difficulty": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-197",
    "question": "What is the name of the facially scarred bodyguard of Mifune",
    "options": ["Han", "Asane", "Kasami", "Okisuke"],
    "answer": "Okisuke",
    "difficulty": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-198",
    "question": "What is the name of the resurrected Sound ninja with a scorch release kekkei genkai",
    "options": ["Hakuno", "Pakura", "Jinin", "Baku"],
    "answer": "Pakura",
    "difficulty": "hard"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-199",
    "question": "What is Rin's surname",
    "options": ["Nohara", "Atari", "Hozuki", "Pakura"],
    "answer": "Nohara",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "id": "naruto-200",
    "question": "What is the name of the six-tailed slug Bijuu",
    "options": ["Chomei", "Matatabi", "Saiken", "Son Goku"],
    "answer": "Saiken",
    "difficulty": "hard"
  }
]








